<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- The name of this section-->
    <string name="section_sections">/sections</string>

    <string-array name="sections_specific_notebook">
        <item>GET: Get list of all sections under a specific notebook</item>
        <item>First we get a list of all notebooks and then query for a list of all sections under the selected notebook. Please select a specific notebook from the drop-down above</item>
        <item>http://dev.onenote.com/docs#/reference/get-sections</item>
        <item>beta</item>
        <item>v1.0</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sections_specific_name">
        <item>GET: Get sections with a specific name</item>
        <item>Query for a list of all sections with a given name. This example shows how to use the \'$filter=name eq \'&lt;term&gt;\' query parameter. Please enter the case-sensitive full section name to look for in the TextBox above</item>
        <item>http://dev.onenote.com/docs#/reference/get-sections</item>
        <item>beta</item>
        <item>v1.0</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="get_all_sections">
        <item>GET: Get list of all sections</item>
        <item>Queries for all sections under all notebooks in OneNote and returns a list</item>
        <item>http://dev.onenote.com/docs#/reference/get-sections</item>
        <item>beta</item>
        <item>v1.0</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="get_metadata_of_section">
        <item>GET: Get metadata of a specific section</item>
        <item>Following the previous example, first we get a list of all sections and then query for the selected section. Please select a specific section from the drop-down above</item>
        <item>http://dev.onenote.com/docs#/reference/get-sections</item>
        <item>beta</item>
        <item>v1.0</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="create_section">
        <item>POST: Create a section in a notebook</item>
        <item>First we get a list of all notebooks and then create an empty section in the selected notebook. Please select a notebook from the drop-down above and enter the new section\'s name in the text box.</item>
        <item>http://dev.onenote.com/docs#/reference/post-sections/v10menotesnotebooksidsections</item>
        <item>beta</item>
        <item>v1.0</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="create_section_in_sectiongroup">
        <item>POST: Create a section in a section group</item>
        <item>First we get a list of all section groups and then create an empty section group in the selected section group. Please select a section group from the drop-down above and enter the new section group\'s name in the text box.</item>
        <item>http://dev.onenote.com/docs#/reference/post-sections/betamenotessectiongroupsidsections</item>
        <item>beta</item>
        <item>beta</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
